beezid.com 2016-04-22

# Privacy

### » Scope

Beezid.com (hereinafter referred to as "Beezid") is a service provided by Beezid Inc. (hereinafter referred to as "Beezid" or "We"). We recognize and respect your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all aspects relating to gathering information while you are visiting the Beezid website (www.beezid.com), how We handle your personal information for our services and all further permissible uses of such information. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new and existing users and is otherwise effective 5 days after being posted on the website.

### » Data Collection

You may visit Beezid at any time without providing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, when you visit our website, We may collect and store your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Beezid, ad data, IP address and standard web log information and information from other companies, including but not limited to, demographic and navigation data.

For you to actively participate in Beezid, We do need some of your personal information, however, once you provide us with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers. We will share your personal information with third parties only in accordance with this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

In connection with your registration and use of Beezid, We may collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address, physical contact and personal information including but not limited to your name, address, date of birth and telephone number;
  * all transactional information based on your activities on Beezid;
  * shipping, billing and other information relating to any purchase or shipping;
  * any correspondence sent to us or by us;
  * financial information, such as your credit card information; and
  * other supplemental information from third parties.

### » Use of Data

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that We may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers;
  * contact you for market research from Beezid by phone, by email or by other means of communication. You may opt out by contacting our support team via email at support@beezid.com or by contacting customer service at 1-877-423-3943.

### » Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters or promotional emails, we will use your name and email address to send the selected communications to you. If you wish to no longer receive these emails you may use the unsubscribe information located with the emails you receive or contact [support@beezid.com](mailto:support@beezid.com) or call customer service at 1-877-423-3943.

### » Disclosure of Personal Data

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to a credit card processor to bill you for services, live chat to assist you if you have questions, fraud investigations and debt collection. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We will also share your personal information with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should We plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, We will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when We believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

### » Your Information on Beezid

Once you have been approved as a registered user with Beezid, you will be required to choose a username. This user name will be displayed throughout Beezid and therefore provided to the public. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, users will not be able to personally identify your activities on Beezid. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.

### » Access, Review and Change of Personal Data

You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to Beezid at any time. However, some of your personal information such as your email address, username, first name, last name, gender, email id and user id can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service at [support@beezid.com](mailto:support@beezid.com). You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or information is inaccurate.

### » Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account

Upon your request, We will close your account as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our General Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. You can delete or deactivate your Beezid account at any time. When you delete your membership, your personal data is removed from our database unless We are required to save the data.

### » The Use of Cookies at our Website

Beezid uses so-called "cookies", which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of "pop-up" windows. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, We would like to point out that turning off these settings may reduce the quality of your experience.

The use of cookies by our affiliates, and tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our affiliates and tracking utility company use session ID cookies such as Google Analytics, LinkShare Affiliate Tracking cookies. You can opt out of the Google Analytical Features that we use by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

. 

### » Web Beacons

Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called Web Beacons that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web Beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, Web Beacons are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Newsletters".

### » Log Files

As is true of most Websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We use third-party tracking services that use log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate to collect usage and volume statistics for security, fraud prevention and marketing.

### » Security Measures

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Your Beezid account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Beezid will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Beezid site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information.

When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). While we strive to protect your personal information, We cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. As examples, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

### » Invite-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to email a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Beezid stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program and to avoid sending repeat requests to the same recipient.

Your friend may contact us at [support@beezid.com](mailto:support@beezid.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### » Links to Third Parties

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Beezid. Please be aware that we, Beezid, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website.

### » Customer Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request that your testimonial be removed please contact us at [support@beezid.com](mailto:support@beezid.com) or 1-877-423-3943.

### » Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@beezid.com](mailto:support@beezid.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### » Facebook Connect

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### » Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes.

We may use facebook.com a third party service provider to conduct these contests; that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

### » Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam

Beezid assures you that We will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms of Use. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and We will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

### » General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 5 days after they are initially posted on the site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### » Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [support@beezid.com](mailto:support@beezid.com) or 10500 Ch. de la Cote de Liesse, Suite 208, Montreal, QC, H8T 1A4, Canada.
